Zeinab Sabori NW10 2LL, London

Mobile number: 07414117575 Email: zsabori82@yahoo.com

Hard-working individual attaining experience in java programming and python. To achieve a highly required standards, I am a creative, quick learner and capable of working in different situations. I am a clear communicator while keeping strong work ethic which would be a fantastic addition to your team.

Kind, friendly and extremely motivated about learning and gaining new experience while working. Technology is a passion of mine besides creating a safe, friendly, and productive environment for everyone, is my top priority.

EXPERIENCE

• Healthcare (Jan 2019 - Current)

Hartwig Care Ltd. - Greater London, England

Supplying a high quality of care and supportive services to people, being reliable, discreet, friendly, and committed to the physical and emotional wellbeing and safety of the client is important.

• Teacher (Oct 2016 - Jan2020)

AL-Huda school - London

Providing support for student with learning difficulty in addition of teaching my own class. Also, I have been as a voluntary teacher assistant in "The School of the Islamic Republic of Iran" (based in London) to gain more experience.

• Administration assistance (2015- Jan 2019)

Noor Trust - Greater London, England

Administrator Assistant dealing with issues such as; updating computer records while using office equipment like printers, photocopiers, and fax machines. Covering reception duties, greeting, and looking after visitors. Dealing with incoming and outgoing post as well as emails and social media enquiries.

Hairdresser

Salon Hijab, Honeypot Lane, Stanmore - London (Feb 2014 - May 2015)

Salon manager

Smart cut - London (Feb 2010 - May 2014)

Managing salon finance, dealing with the customers, consultancy, and advice.

EDUCATION

QA Academy Cloud/ Trainee DevOps Engineer bootcamp (June 2022 till 05/09/2022)

MSC Cyber Security Technology Northumbria University (2021-2022)

Introduction to Packet Tracer (2021)

The complete web development and programming (2020)

MA of Art in Islamic Law, Middlesex University (2017-2019)

BA of Art, Middlesex University (2014-2017)

Studied beauty in The Beauty Academy in London (2012)

College of the city of Westminster studying English literacy &numeracy (2011)

Studying Swedish as a second language in komvu0x Sodervarn in Sweden (07/2006 to 09/2007)

Studying Swedish, English and maths in Komvux Centrum in Sweden (09/2008 to 22/06/2010)

SKILLS

Fluent in English, Arabic, Persian and Swedish.

- Azure, DevOps, and Cloud Computing
- Linux, Windows, Agile, Scrum, GitHub, and python

Teaching, seminars, administration, and office work
Customer Service, Time Management,
Complex Problem Solving, Critical
Thinking
and Computing

Eligible to work in the UK

I am looking to secure a position within your company, where skills, knowledge and earlier experience can be applied.